Chigozirim Ndinechi

ndinechilex@gmail.com +2348146081403 no 109 onitsha/owerri road, mgbidi, Imo state Mgbidi, Imo State

Summary

Skilled website designer and developer with 3 years of experience in working with Wordpress and Django (python web framework). A Highly Analytical mind when it comes to understanding the financial market. A Hardworking and motivated person.

Socials

- Facebook: https://web.facebook.com/chigozirim.ndinechi
- Twitter: https://twitter.com/ChigozirimElife
- Github: https://github.com/chigozirim1999
- Email: ndinechilex@gmail.comPhone Number: 08146081403

Experience

CLASSGOZ NIG LTD

Sales Manager/Finance Manager - Mgbidi, Imo State

09/2015 - 11/2016

I was in charge of all the sales in the company. Under my management there was massive increase in sales, and accounting seamless.

I created a code to help with the accounting with c++, as a beginner then.

When I left to study in the Higher Institution my impact was felt.

MOIRAKING ICT SERVICES CENTER

I.T Teacher - Mgbidi, Imo State

06/2020 - 01/2021

My Job here is solely to Impact ICT Knowledge to Graduates and Secondary Skill Students.

The number of students increased to more 50% during my stay there.

I later played a role of managing the company while teaching, when the manager fell sick for 5months.

SOLANA SAIL ON SOLANA ECOSYSTEM

PITCH DECK DESIGN 09/2021

I designed the Pitch Deck for the Websummit 2021 for a crypto startup SolanaSail, which was hosted in Lisbon, Portugal. It was a remote job

https://twitter.com/SolanaSail is their twitter profile

DRIFT PROTOCOL ON SOLANA ECOSYSTEM

SUPER DRIFTER 09/2021

My Job here is to moderate, assign roles in the community and to test their project before launching. Also to bring ideas that would take the project higher. I also made a video about their project

https://twitter.com/DriftProtocol is their twitter profile

ELIFE CRYPTO

Founder 02/2021 - Present

I started a crypto community on whatsapp to help beginners to get educated about the crypto space and to help them avoid some mistakes, I started it's YouTube channel on August 2021.

I try to grow it at my own pace, while still studying in school.

https://twitter.com/elifecrypto is the twitter profile.

DUMB META

Web Designer and Content Creator

12/2021 - Present

Our role is to help make the brand find a voice online and to think about ways to make the project known and grow. Also to distribute nfts.

Ehub ICT

Web Designer/Developer

I designed the Sales Page for www.ehubict.com to use and make sales.

IFECHIDELU CHARITABLE FOUNDATION

Web Designer/Developer

I created the website of the Charity organization www.ifechidelucf.org

SONADOR MARKET

Web Designer/Developer

09/2020 - 01/2021

I Created Their Website www.sonadormarket.com

Education

Elementary School

LOGOS INTERNATIONAL NURSREY AND PRIMARY SCHOOL Awo-Omamma, Imo State

09/2009

First School Leaving Certificate

Secondary School

 ${\tt LOGOS\ INTERNATIONAL\ SECONDARY\ SCHOOL\ Awo-Ommamma,\ Imo\ State} \\ {\tt WASSCE\ Certificate}$

07/2015

ELECTRONICS AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

NNAMDI AZIKIWE UNIVERSITY, AWKA, ANAMBRA STATE Awka, Anambra

03/2022

- · Graduated with Second Class Lower
- I was the Former Technical Director in my Department in the University, I was in charge of helping students learn hardware and software skills in my department.
- I was the I am the Technical Head in my Church in School (University)

Skills

- Web Design using WordPress
- Python-Django Web Framework for Back-End Web Development
- Front-End Web Development Using HTML and CSS
- · Sales Funnel Building
- · Copy Writing For Marketing
- · Teaching
- Technical Analysis For Financial Markets